When I first started selling
Manulife Vitality,
it was about the rewards.
And the perfect person was someone
who was young and active,
and they were going to be
just a win-win in the product fit.
But it’s actually the complete opposite.
It’s those clients
that you can have the greatest impact
on premiums,
who are the older clients.
Those ones that are looking
for the motivation
for change in their current lifestyle.
Anyone that is either new to the industry
or an advisor that hasn’t put
Manulife Vitality
in front of their clients,
my one piece of advice is
buy it for yourself.
Be an advocate of Manulife Vitality.
Understand it yourself
so you, as an advisor, are equipped
to have that conversation
with your clients
and understand how it works.